convert-me.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy for Convert-me.Com

Effective August 12th, 2004  
Last updated March 14th, 2009

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Convert-me.Com website. On some pages, you can make requests or register to receive access to special site areas. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Email, ICQ, web and other Internet addresses 
  * Phone number 
  * Occupation 
  * Your interests 

You do not have any obligation to supply any personal information. 

Our system may also collect some personal information automatically. The types of personal information collected automatically are:

  * The number of posts you have made to our site forum 
  * The date you registered to receive access to special site areas 
  * Internet addresses (IP addresses) you were accessing the Internet from when posting messages to our site forum 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may collect and use not personally identifying information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit the following pages: 

## The Way We Use Information:

The information you provide about yourself when registering in our site forum is available to other registered members of the forum only. We do not share that information with anyone else.

The mentioned above automatically collected personal information except the Internet addresses you were accessing the Internet from may also be available only to registered members of the forum.

Your Internet address (IP address) is only available to our site staff for technical purposes. This information is not shared with any other party

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing us at [privacy@convert-me.com](mailto:privacy@convert-me.com)

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [privacy@convert-me.com](mailto:privacy@convert-me.com)

<< Return to home page of Convert-me.Com
